

PIMLAPHAT BURAPHATPARINDA

Professional Summary:

Responsible and dependable in Senior Project Coordinator, Executive Assistant, Executive Secretary, Senior Administration and Procurement Coordinator, Senior Engineering Assistant and Project Secretary with knowledge and responsibility, included many good skills in office work with over 10 years of experience with the large oil and gas companies and the leading organizations.

Motivated and resourceful individual with proven years of experience. Possess strong interpersonal and communication skills, included an ability to maintain good relations with clients as well as staff and the team.

Personal Information

Date of Birth: 19 March 1982
Status: Single
Nationality: Thai
Religion: Buddhism
Hobbies: Travel, reading,

movies, music, gym, badminton, jigsaw

puzzles

Date of Availability: 1 Month notice

Skills

- Good Command of Written and Spoken English
- Microsoft Office
- SAP
- Email
- Internet

Education History

- From June 2006 to January 2009
 Master's Degree of Business Administration in Hospitality Management
 Suan Dusit University, Bangkok
 GPA: 3.83
- From June 2000 to February 2004
 Bachelor's Degree of Arts in Tourism and Hotel Minor Subject: French
 Dhurakij Pundit University, Bangkok
 GPA: 3.23

Address: 607/298 On Nut Rd., Suan Luang, Bangkok 10250

E-mail: pimlaphat.buraphatparinda@gmail.com

Tel: 063-669-5636 Line ID: phitchykwang

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/pimlaphat-buraphatparinda-089622144

Employment Experience

Senior Project Coordinator, Promotion and Industry Development and Business Division Digital Economy Promotion Agency (depa), Bangkok (April 2019 - Present)

- Perform coordination and support applying digital technology to business or industry for industrial and business development.
- Coordinate, support and develop the private and public cooperation networks both domestically and internationally.
- Coordinate and support the private sector and the people participating in the project to have access to government services to make the various projects of the center successfully implemented with the private sector.
- Monitor the performance of various projects including regular operations within the organization and recommendations for continuous development.

Executive Assistant to GM

Intertek Testing Services (Thailand) Limited, Bangkok (December 2018 - March 2019)

- Liaise with related parties both internal and external in preparation and necessary arrangement of the requirement documentation to ensure compliance to schedule and project plan on behalf of GM.
- Manage the travel itinerary, accommodation, ticketing for business trips locally and internationally.
- Handle the reimbursement process for any expense from GM, keep record and analysis on the expense monthly report.

Marketing Coordinator, Business Development Department

IBC Industrial Company Limited, Bangkok (July 2018 - November 2018)

- Provide daily administrative tasks to ensure the functionality and coordination of Business Development Department's activities.
- Provide administrative support to the Marketing Team in organizing various projects.
- Collaborate with Marketing Team, Internal Team, Clients and Partners on Marketing Strategy.
- Assist the Bidding Team to prepare, format and edit proposal documents for Bidding.

Senior Administration and Procurement Coordinator

Plan International Inc., Bangkok (July 2017 - June 2018)

- Process and encode the purchase requisition, purchase order and suppliers' invoice by inputting onto the SAP System, the Procurement Data needed by the SAP; purchase requisition (PR), purchase order (PO) and invoice (MIGO).
- Manage petty cash fund and airfare cash funds; making disbursement in compliance with Global Financial Policies.
- Process meeting request; meeting package, accommodation and group dinner to be accurate and appropriate to the budget of the project.
- Process travel request; air ticket (international and domestic flight) and hotel booking to be accurate and appropriate to the budget of the project.

Senior Engineering Assistant

Foster Wheeler (Thailand) Limited, Bangkok (October 2011 -July 2017)

- Support the engineering department with regards to engineering operations and technical/administrative work as required by project.
- Assist with archiving at end of project for project records and ensure that it is carried out in accordance with the project filing index.
- Coordinate the offshore training, included all the logistical requirements for the offshore trips for the project team.
- Prepare and issue monthly progress reports and cost reports to clients.
- Provide the general administrative and all secretarial duties to Project Manager and Project team.